question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States if "
                 "the police sell you illegal substances without revealing themselves.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive "
                 "every tweet by American citizens.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "One of Donald Trump&#039;s 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build "
                 "a border wall between the United States and Mexico.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
